fertur-travel.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

_**At Fertur Peru Travel we take our customer’s privacy very seriously. Below is a full description of our privacy policy.**_

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please feel free to contact our customer service department. You can contact us:

**By phone at 1-877-247-0055  
By email at administrativo @ fertur-travel.com**  
**By letter to Fertur Peru Travel E.I.R.L., Jr. Junin 211, Cercado de Lima, Lima1 Peru.**

When booking with Fertur Peru Travel, we may use or disclose your personal information, either directly or through our agency and booking partners, for the purposes of offering or booking travel services on your behalf, such as your name, age, address, phone number, e-mail address, emergency contact information, passport information, travel medical information (as required), insurance details, ISIC information (where applicable), nationality, residency, nutrition preferences, trip evaluations, travel and accommodation preferences, comments you provide us, trip destination information, and payment-related information. This personal information enables us provide you with trip information, book flights, accommodations, process payments, and provide similar travel services.

Please be aware that Fertur Peru Travel may be required to provide certain personal information to our service providers for the purposes of delivering your experience. For example, foreign travelers who book hotel accommodations in Peru through Fertur Peru Travel will be required to provide passport information that we then share with the hotel in order to waive the “Impuesto General a las Ventas” (IGV – General Sales Tax) that Peruvians and legal residents of Peru are subject to pay. When you book travel services with us, you consent to collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by Fertur Peru Travel — and the corresponding collection and use by its relevant travel partners or suppliers — for the purposes of administering and delivering the travel services we arrange at your request.

As well as a right to access, update and correct information we collect about you, if you are a resident in the UK, European Union or European Economic Area, then you have the following additional rights (in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation, or GDPR):

  * To be told how long your personal information will be retained by us or the basis on which we make decisions about how long we retain your personal information;
  * To require that your personal information is deleted by us, subject to any necessary legal requirements we may have to retain the information;
  * To object to our processing of your personal information or to restrict processing of your personal information (but you must understand we may be unable to provide certain services to you without processing this information);
  * To receive a copy of any personal information we hold about you in a portable format;
  * To lodge a complaint with a relevant supervising authority (for example the Information Commissioner’s Office in the UK).

When you inquire about services via our on-line forms, you may receive communications from us, aside from service-related emails, including newsletters, surveys, promotional offers, and special announcements. If you do not wish to receive these communications, please be sure to opt-out by un-checking the check box on the “Contact Us” page above the “Submit” button before submitting your request. (This check box is normally left unchecked by default.)

We do use a third party email service provider. All emails that you receive will contain an UNSUBSCRIBE link should you decide you do not want any further emails. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing us at administrativo @ fertur-travel.com with “unsubscribe” written in the subject line, by calling at 1-877-247-0055, or postal mail at Fertur Peru Travel E.I.R.L., Jr. Junin 211, Cercado de Lima, Lima1 Peru.

When you contact Fertur Peru Travel to inquire about travel services or for other purposes, we may attempt a good faith effort to verify your identity based on the information you provide in order to make sure you are who you represent yourself to be before fulfilling your request. We do this for your protection as well as ours.

We consider your data to be private and confidential, and we hold ourselves to the highest standards of trust and fiduciary duty in their safekeeping and use. Fertur Peru Travel E.I.R.L, will not release information collected about you unless we receive your prior consent or we are required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Websites or business.

We also routinely collect information about customer satisfaction. This collected information consists of name, nationality and email address, as well as trip details such as dates, destination, passenger information and the number of people in your party. This information is used to address any concerns you might raise. The data is also analyzed in an aggregated form to improve our services.

With your permission, we may use your name and excerpted comments in designated areas of our Websites and services as well as other marketing materials used to promote Fertur Peru Travel E.I.R.L. We _do not_ share, sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties for their promotional use. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties, except when expressly necessary to provide the travel services you book with us.

We post customer reviews on our Websites which may contain personally identifiable information such as the customer’s name and image. We do obtain the customers’ prior consent to post their names along with their written review and any photographs they send to us or expressly allow us to use.

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on our Websites. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our sites. We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our sites and to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our sites in the aggregate, such as volume and origin traffic. We also retain log files (e.g. browser type, page views, and how the user entered and exited the site). We collect, retain and use this information solely for the purpose of better understanding our users and their use of our websites. This allows us to better serve and hone our client base.

Third party vendors publish Fertur Peru Travels’ ads on the Internet. These third party vendors use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website. (You can learn about opting out of third-party usage of cookies for advertising purposes by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/.) We may also use third party services, such as Google Analytics, to help us gather and analyze data about the areas that you visit on our websites to evaluate and improve the customer experience and our published content. This information is not linked to the user’s personal information.

The security of your personal information is very important to us. When customers enter sensitive information on our registration or order forms or send us scanned documentation, we urge them not to  do so via open email. Instead we strongly suggest they send that information via Fax or a secure, encrypted [www.Hushmail.com](https://www.hushmail.com/) Premium Business account that we maintain.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

For the convenience of our customers, Fertur Peru Travel offers several secure on-line payment methods and accepts all major credit cards. In the case of payments made via VisaNet Perú or WeTravel/Stripe or PayPal, the customer is subject to the privacy policies of those third party services. As part of our [Terms and Conditions](https://fertur-travel.com/pdf/booking_policy_english.pdf?x29015) we require that our customers expressly understand and agree that Fertur Peru Travel shall not be liable for any problem that may arise through the use of those third party services, including the mishandling of the customer’s personal information.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, feel free email us.

### Changes in the Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it regularly. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**(UPDATED MAY 25, 2018)**

**Next>**
